ED]
We are now at Joypolis Sports Aeon Sendai Nakayama store!
Yay!
We're here!
Mountain bugs!
Oh! Look out! Look out!
Yes, that's why I'm here!
Mountain bugs! Mountain bugs!
This is... oh, my gosh!
Ta-da!
About 30 kinds of sports and entertainment contents are here for your enjoyment!
Entertainment?
This is a sports amusement facility where you can play all the entertainment contents you want!
Yay!
That's great!
I've been curious about this place for a while, so now I'm here.
Yes, we've been saying that we wanted to come here for a long time.
I'm so excited!
And at Joypolis Sports AEON Sendai Nakayama
We have a special event for you this time!
What is it?
The name of the event is "5 games"!
Yay!
Five games!
This time, we are going to play 5 games!
We will divide into two teams and challenge five different contents!
The team with more wins will be the winner!
Yay!
The teams will be divided into two teams, A team will be Rine and Kanene, and
The B team is Hinano and Ryu.
Do you have a team name? Do you two have a name?
Yes, we do.
Okay, go ahead.
Seino
We are the 2023 Joypolis Tournament champions!
Oh! That looks strong!
They were the favorites to win last year's Joypolis 2023!
These are the two candidates!
You couldn't call yourself that?
Is that right?
No, no, no, it's true!
Yes, it's true!
That's great!
Yes, it is!
I can't lose!
Yes, it is! We're not winning!
We're going to beat the contenders?
I see! That's what I thought!
What about the A team?
We're the "A" team.
Team sexy!
Why didn't you say that?
Why didn't you say anything?
You just decided on a color, didn't you?
So you want to be sexy on your own?
I see what you mean!
There's a lot of things you can do with it.
Sexy!
Sexy?
Let's face it!
I'm going to challenge you to five different kinds of sexy kimokos!
Then make the script sexy!
Stop it!
What?
No?
Physical?
Is that what this is?
Oh, shit!
Oh, I see!
I'm going to do it!
And!
This time, for the losing team
There will be a penalty game!
Sexy!
The penalty game this time is
Yes!
It's frustration!
This time, the penalty game is to feel sorry if you lose!
That's so sweet!
This is the first time for me to be punished!
You're so kind!
Kind face!
Sure, but, I'm so frustrated!
Too chatty!
I'm sorry!
My apologies!
Yes, I know, I was just saying that frustration is a punishment.
Like this, I was also a star who never loses at anything!
That's for sure!
I hope I can convey the fun!
Yes!
Let's try the first one!
Let's go for the first run!
Next time notice
The first challenge is MORQUE!
Now, Mr. Okuda, a staff member, will explain about MORC.
Hello, Okuda-san!
Hello.
I'm sorry.
I would like to explain the game.
You throw a morc and knock down picolli.
If you knock one down, you get the score written on it.
If you knock down two, you will get two points.
If you knock down 2 morcs, you will get 3 points except for the score.
This time, you will be challenged with a special rule that will give you an impulse score of 15 points.
If you go over 15 points, it will come back to 10 points again
Thank you very much.
It's a game that requires a lot of brain and body.
First offender and second offender will be decided by a game of rock-paper-scissors-scissors.
I'd like to decide by janken (rock-paper-scissors-scissors).
I'll do my best.
Go for it, Yuneko!
You're beautiful.
How to win?
Yes, sexy.
Now, guess the 15 points!
Rock, paper, scissors, rock, paper, scissors!
Which one of you would like to be the first?
Which is better?
We'll see how it goes.
Let's go ahead.
Okay, let's go first.
Cheese Sexy will go first.
Okay, I'll throw out the first pitch.
Yes!
I'll do my best!
Sexy!
Here I go!
Ha!
Oh!
All of it?
Throw it all!
What? What do you mean?
What?
Power, start with the gun?
Strike!
That's great! Three more!
That's it! Three more!
That's great!
Oh, my gosh!
So powerful!
Sexy power!
Gorilla!
Oh, man!
Oh, no! Oh, no!
Sexy has faded!
Sexy gorilla!
Sexy!
Ha-ha-ha!
I can do anything!
Next, 12 points!
Oh, so it's a 12!
That's great!
Yes! Let the power of last year's winner flow through you.
Oh, I didn't win it!
He was a contender!
We were the favorites! I will do my best with all my might!
Go for it!
You can do it!
You can do it! You can do it!
Baito!
It doesn't matter how you throw it!
Yeah!
Oh! That's good!
It's good, isn't it?
Six!
Oh, no, no, no!
Thank you very much!
Aim for three!
Yes!
3 throws are next, so it's easy to aim!
Nice! Mr. Cullen!
I'm going for it!
Then I want it!
Go for it!
I'm going for three points!
That's gonna be tough!
Ah! You're strong!
You can do it next time, Karen!
Oh! Really?
That was close!
That was sexy!
How many more points do I have?
Nine! Nine!
Nine! I'm not going for that part!
I'll try my best!
Go for it!
Aim for the nine!
He says it doesn't matter how you throw it!
That's it!
Here we go!
Oh! It's over!
That's great!
A coherent throw!
Nice try!
I'm going for 3!
Good luck!
All right! Here we go!
Wow! That was close!
That's about right!
So close!
You can do it!
Go for it!
Isn't that a 9?
You can beat 9,
I see what you mean!
Or you can go for the 9,
A few more!
Let's just get some more!
Anything!
Let's knock some down!
Come on!
Fyor! Fyor!
That's good!
Nice!
That means we've got 5?
Five!
Harder!
Where could he be?
What do you do, go for three or go for three?
You're right, three!
Three is faster!
What do you think?
Can I go for three?
Let's go for three!
I'm going for it!
Oh! One for now!
That's so great! You can do it!
Well, if you aim for the next one,
But you can still get one!
If you knock one down...
Oh! No, no, no!
No, no, no! It's so hard!
It's so hard!
Oh, no! It's so hard!
Five more?
You can't do five!
No! Come on!
What do you want, mija?
Hmm?
You want five or five?
Six!
Not five?
It's five!
Where can we get five?
No! This one!
Can we just knock it down for now?
Can't we just take down the middle five?
No!
You're so cute!
No, you can't!
Let's do it!
That's good!
That's great! That's great!
That's great! Out of the blue!
Did we go over?
It's this way!
But we've only got five more to go!
Oh! That's great!
All you have to do is aim for one!
Can anyone see them?
I'm going for it!
Come on!
Oh! Oh, no!
Where's my handkerchief?
It flew away!
You're such a tomboy!
Mynya, hang in there!
Hang in there!
Do something!
Go, go, go!
Go!
Already like this?
Oh, no.
Oh no.
That was close.
Oh, no.
Come back.
That was close.
Next. Next.
Next.
This is hard.
It's hard.
Time is zero, zero, zero.
It's so cool.
What's that? It's true.
It feels good.
Here we go.
How do you throw this?
It's hard.
Yes, it's hard.
Go for it!
Aaah!
That's a tough one.
What was it, 5?
I wonder if I can do it.
Go, go, go, go, go, go!
We like blue clouds.
Oh, no!
That was fun.
It's good.
We like red.
I'm gonna go for it.
I'm gonna put on some underwear.
But I don't know.
You want to give it a shot?
Really?
Let's give it a shot.
Aah! That was close!
Aah! Oh! Oh! Oh!
Candy ride.
That's good. I wanted one so bad just now.
Here we go.
Aaaaah!
5 again!
5 obsessed, winner Corporal.
Are you ready to go?
Gudge, mate. Gudge, mate.
Thank you.
Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Five!
I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it!
I'm so frustrated.
I'm so disappointed.
It's frustrating.
I'm so frustrated. This is a fight of 5.
It's a fight of 5. I'm...
Five in the middle.
Five is mine.
I'm in, I'm in, I'm in.
Be careful. 11 is in there.
I've got 11. Push.
Push! Push! Push!
Come on!
Okay, good luck. Let's eat.
Wow.
Eight minutes. Eight.
You don't need eight minutes. You can do your best.
You don't need five minutes. You can do your best.
Okay, good luck, good luck, good luck.
What happens if I hit 10 now?
It's like this with a hammer.
What if I take down a few of them?
It slipped through! That's too close!
I'm going for 10, 11, 12...
I'm going for it!
Number one!
Eleven!
Eleven, so five!
Battle of 5.
I'm obsessed with this place.
Five balls is not so easy.
I'll do my best!
Go for it!
Take down those two over there,
I'll try the other three.
Sure thing. There it is.
Here it goes!
Too close!
That means 5 again.
5.
Five.
A haunted house of 5.
Even if it's just one 5.
Yes!
Yes, indeed.
I see 8 ahead of 5.
I'm going!
Yay!
Yeah!
Sexy!
Nisai is sexy!
A voice of regret. I'm frustrated.
Regretful?
Slightly so of the winner, I guess.
Please let us know.
I had a feeling of regret.
Seriously.
I am frustrated.
I will practice a lot this year with this feeling of frustration in my heart.
Please help me.
Congratulations!
Mork, what's wrong?
I am so happy and alone.
So, I entered MORQUE.
First round.
Mork is won by Team Sexy.
It was quite difficult.
It was difficult. It was a good battle.
It was fun.
It was fun and exciting.
I thought I'd let them off the hook for at least two wins.
I see.
That's right.
I'm grateful.
We're grateful because you're weak.
Yes, yes.
She's sexy, isn't she?
She's a bewitching woman.
Yes, I am. So that's the end of the first round.
Yay!
It's fun.
I'm having so much fun.
That's great.
Okay, Mr. Michimi.
Mr. Michimi.
Let's go to the second round!
Let's go for Round 2!
The next event is the human tower battle!
This is the tower battle here.
Let me explain the rules.
There is a green bag here.
The teams take turns standing on the green bag, for example, Karen, Mew, Rine, Hinano, Karen, Mew, and so on.
The enemy team takes turns standing in the green bag.
Then they pause.
Then, a picture is taken of you on the screen in front of you,
Then, the teams would pile on top of each other,
The team that collapses loses.
I see.
I hope everyone understands the rules as you watch the game.
Okay.
Shall we play rock-paper-scissors?
Yes, let's play rock-paper-scissors-scissors.
First, let's play rock-paper-scissors-scissors.
Yes, I'll play Janken first.
First, goo, then rock-paper-scissors!
Yay!
Oh, I lost.
I lost.
So, do you want to play first or second?
Next time, go first.
Oh! Okay.
OK.
Okay, let's do it together!
[ED]
[chimes]
[Laughter]
Oh, it's starting already?
It's starting?
All right.
I'm so excited, I'm barefoot.
I'll do it.
Oh, my God.
It's hard.
Mandom.
This is hard.
I don't know what to do.
Oh, I see.
We can move around.
Wow.
Oh, no, no, no.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
That was fast.
No way.
Just one more.
It's okay.
I liked it better before.
Yeah, it was.
I just wanted to stand here.
What do you want me to do?
Next.
I'll go next.
Excuse me, sir.
I'm sorry.
It's so small.
I'll fight.
What's that?
Huh?
Oh, here he comes.
He's cute.
You're supposed to stand back.
Oh, that's nice. That's cute.
Oh, he's so cute!
Why are you falling over?
So cute! Why did you fall over?
Why did you fall over?
Come on, Kane-kun! Hang in there!
I did something weird.
Eh, my knee...
You look scared. Scary.
Wow! Oh, my God!
He's being bullied.
Hang in there. Hang in there.
Wow! That's great!
Really? That's amazing!
That's amazing! Oh, man.
Oh!
Wait! What do I do?
This is so fun!
This is hard.
It's difficult.
I see what you mean.
That's great. I'll be exposed again.
Amazing. That's great.
Okay, I'll do the person on the other side.
What should we do next?
Sprouts.
Great. Sprouts. Sprouts.
Flat feet.
Foot flat.
Amazing. New car and new glasses.
That's hard to do.
Yes, it is.
That's good. It's good.
Come on.
There's something I can do.
Hang in there, Mi-chan.
Hang in there.
Wow!
Ura! Ura!
I've been waiting for you! Ura!
Urra!
Ura!
Wait! What the hell!
It's gonna work! It's gonna work!
Next! I want to build it!
That's great!
Come on! Come on!
Isn't this good?
We're done!
Cute!
I can do it!
Almost!
Oh, my gosh!
Ha-ha-ha!
You look so strong!
Nobody's watching!
It's so much fun!
I want to do it again!
I wanna do it again!
Yes, so we have a winner!
Yes, we have!
This time, in 2023
JPT
The JPT winner
I'm the JPT winner!
I was strong!
I like the bridge!
I love the bridge!
I'm so stacked!
It's a game I play all the time!
That's for sure!
It was fun!
I want to play it again!
It's too much fun!
Yes! Let's do it!
It's so much fun! This is so much fun!
It's so much fun!
Then I'm out!
Looks like a difficult exercise
Looks very common
Looks addictive!
Looks like a cute animal
I like it.
Doesn't look too hard.
Yeah, it is.
Oh, that's me.
How do I get in?
I want to get in.
I feel like I'm supporting this moment
LOL!
LOL
BGM
Only a little more.
It was just a moment.
I cried a little bit.
So I just couldn't say a little more.
I'd like to go private next time.
The first round is sexy.
Round two is the winner.
So I'd like to move on to the third round.
The next competition is foot dance.
Yes, so we have a big foot dance ice cream here.
This time, I'd like to play by our rules.
It doesn't matter what the strategy of the dance is.
The point is to hit the target with the foot on the ice.
We're going to do it in the bathroom today.
Yes!
Okay, let's go ahead and do this too.
Yeah, let's jack this up.
Go!
Go for it!
That's all I see!
Let's go!
First goo!
First one's a goo!
Yeah!
Okay, so...
We'll go first.
I'd like to go first.
Yes!
Let's go!
Okay, I'll go first.
I'll go first. I'm aiming for 19 points.
The top and bottom. Go for it.
17 points!
Go!
That's great!
I love it.
I want to turn it around.
20 points or more.
That's for sure.
Yes, that's right.
I can go for 2.
I can do it with 2.
50 points in the middle.
What? Is that right?
I can do it.
50 in the middle!
Oh, no! That's too close!
That's a 12.
That's 29!
That's great! What should I do?
That's amazing!
What should I do?
I'm going for 20.
Go!
He says, "One more time.
He's so sweet! So sweet!
I'm terrible at ball games.
Oh, yeah.
I'd like to get a point for sure.
For sure.
Ahhh!
I'll do my best. I'll do my best.
This is 17 points.
Seventeen points.
Amazing.
That's very kind. 17 points.
It's good.
That's a good match.
Then, I'll aim for 50 points.
Yes.
Go for it.
Call me a red sheet.
I love the table.
Team Sexy scored 29,
2023 is 30.
Well, I'm going for 50.
I'll read 2023.
Aim for 50 points!
Go for it!
You all thought I was being violent, didn't you?
Yes, I did.
It's fun! I didn't want people to hate me.
But you were so strong, you might want to kick it while you're trying to stick it to them first.
Go for it!
Shall we do it again?
It's hard.
On the contrary. You're amazing.
I'm sorry if I lied to you.
I'm sorry if I lied to you, but I've been invited to do a project.
Let's go for it.
I'll do my best.
Oh, three points.
That's great. That's a good match.
Let's see how many points we can get.
How many points do I get?
So is that a good place to start? I don't know.
I'll just kick it.
The ball is my friend.
Oh! It's right in the middle.
Seventeen.
But you can't tell if it comes from that way.
It's right in the middle.
17, so it's anti-contraction?
That's right.
One more pitch.
But if it comes from that side, you'll never know.
That's just luck.
I'll take the nervous one.
Nervous?
That's scary.
Oh, yeah.
You're supposed to use this.
I'm good at not being nervous.
Ha-ha-ha.
That's because I'm nervous.
Sports should be fun, right?
I got it!
Oh, cool.
You're not 17?
Not 17?
Seventeen.
Yay!
Whew.
Let's see who's in the draw this time.
2023, the Joypolis Tournament winner.
That was a great fight. You were quick at times.
No, no, no, no, it was a good fight.
It was pretty hard. Yeah, I would have liked to have scored 50.
It was difficult. It was difficult to adjust.
Try it. Okay, so it's two against one now.
We still have two more to go, so we'll move on to the next one.
Let's go!
Ready, go!
On to the ko-ho!
Whoo!
Wah!
Wow!
Oh, no! Oh, no!